<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.ktorrent.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">К‑торент</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑торент</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ktorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KTorrent</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKTorrentxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KTorrent</name>
  <summary>BitTorrent Client</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Veceru BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Client de BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Client de BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Klient pro BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">BitTorrent-Programm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Εφαρμογή BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">BitTorrent Client</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Cliente de BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Client BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Cliente de BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Client BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">BitTorrent-cliënt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Klient BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Cliente de BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Клиент BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">BitTorrent Klient</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Битторент клијент</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Bittorrent klijent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Битторент клијент</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Bittorrent klijent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Dataflödesprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">BitTorrent İstemcisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Клієнт BitTorrent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxBitTorrent Clientxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">BitTorrent 客户端</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KTorrent is a BitTorrent application by KDE which allows you to download files using
      the BitTorrent protocol. It enables you to run multiple torrents at the same time and
      comes with extended features to make it a full-featured client for BitTorrent.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KTorrent és una aplicació de BitTorrent creada per la comunitat KDE que us permetrà descarregar fitxers utilitzant el protocol BitTorrent. Permet executar múltiples torrents alhora i ve amb característiques esteses per fer-lo un client complet per a BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KTorrent és una aplicació de BitTorrent creada per la comunitat KDE que vos permetrà descarregar fitxers utilitzant el protocol BitTorrent. Permet executar múltiples torrents alhora i ve amb característiques esteses per fer-lo un client complet per a BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KTorrent ist ein BitTorrent-Programm von KDE. Sie können damit Dateien über das BitTorrent-Protokoll herunterladen. Mehrere Torrents lassen sich gleichzeitig ausführen. KTorrent hat zusätzliche Fähigkeiten und ist damit ein mit allen Funktionen ausgestattetes Dienstprogramm für BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KTorrent είναι μια εφαρμογή BitTorrent από το KDE την οποία σας επιτρέπει να κάνετε λήψεις αρχείων με χρήσητ του πρωτοκόλλου BitTorrent. Σας δίνει τη δυνατότητα να εκετελείτε πολλά torrents ταυτόχρονα και συνοδεύεται με εκτεταμένες λειτουργίες για μια πλήρη χαρακτηριστικών εφαρμογή BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KTorrent is a BitTorrent application by KDE which allows you to download files using the BitTorrent protocol. It enables you to run multiple torrents at the same time and comes with extended features to make it a full-featured client for BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KTorrent  es una aplicación bitTorrent de KDE que le permite descargar archivos usando el protocolo BitTorrent. Permite ejecutar varios torrents al mismo tiempo e incluye características extendidas para convertilo en un cliente completo para BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KTorrent est une application BitTorrent par KDE qui vous permet de télécharger des fichiers en utilisant le protocole BitTorrent. Il peut gérer plusieurs torrents en même temps et possède des fonctionnalités étendues qui en font un client complet pour BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KTorrent é un aplicativo de BitTorrent por KDE que permítelle descargar ficheiros usando o protocolo BitTorrent. Permítelle executar varios torrents ao mesmo tempo e inclúe funcionalidades adicionais que o converten nun cliente de BitTorrent completo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KTorrent è un'applicazione BitTorrent della comunità KDE, che ti permette di scaricare i file usando il protocollo BitTorrent. Ti consente di avviare contemporaneamente torrent multipli, e ti arriva con funzionalità estese, che lo rendono un client di BitTorrent ricco di funzionalità.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KTorrent is een BitTorrent-toepassing door KDE die u in staat stelt bestanden te downloaden met het BitTorrent-protocol. U kunt meerdere torrents tegelijk doen en het komt met uitgebreide functies om het een client voor BitTorrent te laten zijn met alle mogelijkheden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KTorrent jest aplikacją BitTorrent stworzoną w ramach KDE, która umożliwia ci pobieranie przy użyciu protokołu BitTorrent. Umożliwia ci uruchamianie wielu torrentów w tym samym czasie i jest wyposażona w dodatkowe możliwości tworzące z niej pełnego klienta dla BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KTorrent é uma aplicação de BitTorrent do KDE que lhe permite obter ficheiros pelo protocolo BitTorrent. Ele permite-lhe executar várias torrentes ao mesmo tempo e vem com funcionalidades alargadas que o tornam um cliente pleno de funcionalidades para o BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">К‑торент је програм из КДЕ‑а којим можете да преузимате фајлове преко протокола битторент. Омогућава покретање више торената истовремено и пружа разноврсне проширене могућности, што га чини га свеобухватним битторент клијентом.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">KTorrent je program iz KDE‑a kojim možete da preuzimate fajlove preko protokola Bittorrent. Omogućava pokretanje više torenata istovremeno i pruža raznovrsne proširene mogućnosti, što ga čini ga sveobuhvatnim bittorrent klijentom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑торент је програм из КДЕ‑а којим можете да преузимате фајлове преко протокола битторент. Омогућава покретање више торената истовремено и пружа разноврсне проширене могућности, што га чини га свеобухватним битторент клијентом.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">KTorrent je program iz KDE‑a kojim možete da preuzimate fajlove preko protokola Bittorrent. Omogućava pokretanje više torenata istovremeno i pruža raznovrsne proširene mogućnosti, što ga čini ga sveobuhvatnim bittorrent klijentom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ktorrent är ett dataflödesprogram av KDE som låter dig ladda ner filer med protokollet BitTorrent. Det möjliggör att hantera flera dataflöden samtidigt och levereras med utökade funktioner som gör det till en fullfjädrad klient för BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KTorrent, KDE tarafından geliştirilen, BitTorrent protokolünü kullanarak dosyaları indirmenize izin veren bir BitTorrent uygulamasıdır. Aynı anda birden fazla torrent çalıştırabilmenizi ve BitTorrent için tam özellikli bir istemci yapabilmeniz için genişletilmiş özellikler ile birlikte geliştirilmiştir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KTorrent — програма для обміну даними торентів, створена розробниками KDE, за допомогою якої ви можете отримувати і розповсюджувати дані на основі протоколу BitTorrent. Ця програма надає вам змогу одночасно обмінюватися даними декількох торентів. Також передбачено додаткові можливості, які роблять програму повноцінною клієнтською частиною для обміну даними BitTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKTorrent is a BitTorrent application by KDE which allows you to download files using the BitTorrent protocol. It enables you to run multiple torrents at the same time and comes with extended features to make it a full-featured client for BitTorrent.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KTorrent 是 KDE 提供的 BT 下载应用。支持同时运行多个种子，并具有多种扩展特性，是一个全功能的 BT 客户端。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Carauterístiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Recursos:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Queuing of torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Cua dels torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Cua dels torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Verwaltung von Warteschlangen für Torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Ουρές από torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Queuing of torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Encolado de torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Mise en file d'attente des torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Consulta de torrents.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Accodamento dei torrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Torrents in de wachtrij zetten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kolejkowanie torrentów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Fila de espera de torrentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Загрузка торрентов по очереди</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Стављање торената у ред.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Stavljanje torenata u red.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Стављање торената у ред.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Stavljanje torenata u red.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Köa dataflöden</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Torrent kuyruğu</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Черга торентів</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxQueuing of torrentsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">队列种子</li>
      <li>Global and per torrent speed limits</li>
      <li xml:lang="ast">Llendes de velocidá globales y per torrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Límits de velocitat global i per torrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Límits de velocitat global i per torrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Geschwindigkeitsbegrenzungen global und für den einzelnen Torrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Καθολικά και ανά torrent όρια ταχύτητας</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Global and per torrent speed limits</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Límites de velocidad globales e individuales</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Limites de vitesse globales et par torrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Límites de velocidade globais e por torrent.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Limiti di velocità globali e per torrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Globale en per torrent snelheidslimieten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Ograniczenie prędkości globalne i na torrenta</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Limites de velocidades globais e por torrentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Общие и отдельные для каждого торрента ограничения скорости</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Ограничења брзине, глобална и по торенту.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Ograničenja brzine, globalna i po torentu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Ограничења брзине, глобална и по торенту.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Ograničenja brzine, globalna i po torentu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Hastighetsbegränsningar, allmänna och per dataflöde</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Evrensel ve torrent'e özel hız sınırı</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Обмеження на швидкість на загальному рівні і для окремих торентів</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxGlobal and per torrent speed limitsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">全局限速和单个种子限速</li>
      <li>Previewing of certain file types, build in (video and audio)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista prèvia de certs tipus de fitxers, construït en (vídeo i àudio)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista prèvia de certs tipus de fitxers, construït en (vídeo i àudio)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Eingebaute Vorschau für bestimmte Dateitypen (Video und Audio)</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Προεπισκόπηση συγκεκριμένων τύπων αρχείων, ενσωματωμένη (με βίντεο και ήχο)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Previewing of certain file types, build in (video and audio)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista previa de ciertos tipos de archivo, vídeo y audio incorporados</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Aperçu en interne de certains types de fichiers (vidéo et audio)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Previsualización de certos tipos de ficheiros, incluída (vídeo e son).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Anteprima integrata per alcuni tipi di file (video e audio)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Voorbeelden van bepaalde bestandstypen bekijken, ingebouwd (video en geluid)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Podgląd pewnych rodzajów plików, wbudowany odtwarzacz filmów i dźwięku</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Antevisão incorporada de alguns tipos de ficheiros (vídeo e áudio)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Предварительный просмотр файлов некоторых типов (видео, звук)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Преглед појединих типова фајлова, уграђено (видео и аудио).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Pregled pojedinih tipova fajlova, ugrađeno (video i audio).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Преглед појединих типова фајлова, уграђено (видео и аудио).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Pregled pojedinih tipova fajlova, ugrađeno (video i audio).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Förhandsgranskning av vissa filtyper inbyggd (video och ljud)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Belli dosya tipleri için ön izleme, gömülü (video ve ses)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перегляд даних файлів деяких типів, вбудований (відео і звукові дані)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPreviewing of certain file types, build in (video and audio)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">内置的文件预览功能 (视频和音频)</li>
      <li>Importing of partially or fully downloaded files</li>
      <li xml:lang="ast">Importación de ficheros baxaos dafechu o parcialmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Importació de fitxers descarregats parcialment o del tot</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Importació de fitxers descarregats parcialment o del tot</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Teilweise oder vollständig heruntergeladene Dateien werden importiert</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εισαγωγή αποσπασματικώς ή πλήρως ληφθέντων αρχείων</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Importing of partially or fully downloaded files</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Importación de archivos descargados parcial o totalmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Import de fichiers partiellement ou totalement téléchargés</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Importación de ficheiros descargados total ou parcialmente.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Importazione di file parzialmente o totalmente scaricati</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gedeeltelijk of volledig gedownloade bestanden importeren</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Impot częściowo lub w pełni pobranych plików</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Importação de ficheiros transferidos parcialmente ou por completo</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Импорт частично или полностью загруженных файлов</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Увоз делимично или потпуно преузетих фајлова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Uvoz delimično ili potpuno preuzetih fajlova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Увоз делимично или потпуно преузетих фајлова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Uvoz delimično ili potpuno preuzetih fajlova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Import av partiellt eller fullständigt nerladdade filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kısmi veya tam indirilmiş dosyaları içe aktarma</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імпортування частково або повністю звантажених файлів</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxImporting of partially or fully downloaded filesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">导入部分或完全下载的文件</li>
      <li>File prioritization for multi-file torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Priorització de fitxers per a torrents amb múltiples fitxers</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Priorització de fitxers per a torrents amb múltiples fitxers</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Dateipriorisierung für Torrents mit mehreren Dateien</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Παραχώρηση προτεραιότητας σε αρχείο σε torrent με πολλά αρχεία</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">File prioritisation for multi-file torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Priorización de archivos para torrents multiarchivo</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Ordre de priorité des fichiers et pour les torrents multi-fichiers</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Priorización de ficheiros para os torrents con varios ficheiros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Priorità dei file per i torrent multi-file</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bestandsprioriteit instellen multi-bestand-torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Priorytety dla wieloplikowych torrentów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Prioritização de torrentes multi-ficheiros</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Приоритеты файлов для торрентов с несколькими файлами</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Задавање приоритета по фајлу у торентима са више фајлова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Zadavanje prioriteta po fajlu u torentima sa više fajlova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Задавање приоритета по фајлу у торентима са више фајлова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Zadavanje prioriteta po fajlu u torentima sa više fajlova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Filprioritering för dataflöden med flera filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Birden çok dosya barındıran torrentler için dosya önceliklendirme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Визначення пріоритетів файлів у торентах, які складаються з декількох файлів</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFile prioritization for multi-file torrentsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">多文件种子设定文件优先级</li>
      <li>Selective downloading for multi-file torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Descàrrega selectiva per a torrents amb múltiples fitxers</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Descàrrega selectiva per a torrents amb múltiples fitxers</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">In Torrents mit mehreren Dateien können einzelne Dateien zum Herunterladen ausgewählt werden.</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Επιλεκτική λήψη για torrent με πολλά αρχεία</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Selective downloading for multi-file torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Descarga selectiva de torrents multiarchivo</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Téléchargement sélectif pour les torrents multi-fichiers</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Descarga selectiva para torrents con varios ficheiros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Scaricamento selettivo per i torrent multi-file</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Selectief downloaden van multi-bestand-torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wybiórcze pobieranie dla wieloplikowych torrentów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Transferência selectiva para torrentes multi-ficheiros</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Выборочная загрузка файлов из торрентов с несколькими файлами</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Селективно преузимање у торентима са више фајлова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Selektivno preuzimanje u torentima sa više fajlova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Селективно преузимање у торентима са више фајлова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Selektivno preuzimanje u torentima sa više fajlova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Selektiv nerladdning för dataflöden med flera filer</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Birden çok dosya barındıran torrentler için seçimli indirme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вибіркове отримання даних торентів, які складаються з декількох файлів</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSelective downloading for multi-file torrentsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">多文件种子可选下载指定文件</li>
      <li>Kick/ban peers with an additional IP Filter dialog for list/edit purposes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Expulsa/veta els parells amb un diàleg de filtre d'IP addicional per a propòsits de llista/edició</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Expulsa/veta els parells amb un diàleg de filtre d'IP addicional per a propòsits de llista/edició</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Gegenstellen zwangsweise trennen oder verbannen mit Hilfe eines zusätzlichen IP-Filterdialogs. Die IP-Einträge können in diesem Dialog angezeigt und bearbeitet werden.</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αποκλεισμός κόμβων με επιπλέον διάλογο IP φίλτρου για σκοπούς λίστας/επεξεργασίας</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Kick/ban peers with an additional IP Filter dialogue for list/edit purposes</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Expulsión/bloqueo de pares con diálogo de filtro IP adicional para propósitos de listar/editar</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Exclusion/bannissement de pairs avec une fenêtre additionnelle pour lister/modifier les filtres d'IP</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Expulsar e prohibir parceiros cun diálogo adicional de filtraxe por IP para listar e editar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Caccia/metti al bando i nodi con un'ulteriore finestra di dialogo di filtro IP per elencarli e modificarli</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Start/stop peers met een extra dialoog voor IP-filteren voor weergeven/bewerken</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wykopywanie/banowanie uczestników  z dodatkowym filtrem IP do celów edycji i wyświetlania</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Banir/expulsar as máquinas com uma janela adicional de filtros de IP's para fins de listagem/edição</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность отключения о блокирования пиров. Список заблокированных пиров можно редактировать в диалоге IP-фильтра.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Избацивање/забрањивање вршњака преко дијалога за филтрирање ИП‑ова (листање и уређивање).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Izbacivanje/zabranjivanje vršnjaka preko dijaloga za filtriranje IP‑ova (listanje i uređivanje).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Избацивање/забрањивање вршњака преко дијалога за филтрирање ИП‑ова (листање и уређивање).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Izbacivanje/zabranjivanje vršnjaka preko dijaloga za filtriranje IP‑ova (listanje i uređivanje).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Sparka ut eller förbjud deltagare med en ytterligare IP-filtreringsdialogruta i listnings- och redigeringssyfte</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Listeleme/Düzenleme amaçları için ilave bir IP Süzgeci penceresin ile eşleri atma/engelleme</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Викидання/Блокування вузлів за допомогою додаткового діалогового вікна фільтрування за IP (список і редагування записів)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxKick/ban peers with an additional IP Filter dialog for list/edit purposesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">踢掉/屏蔽对等点，并可以用 IP 过滤器查看和编辑列表</li>
      <li>UDP tracker support</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport del seguidor UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport del seguidor UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Podpora trackerů UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für UDP-Tracker</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη ανιχνευτή UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">UDP tracker support</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Uso de rastreador UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion des trackers UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade con localizadores UDP.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto ai server traccia UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning van UDP-tracker</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa serwera śledzącego UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte a localizadores por UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка трекеров UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за УДП пратиоце.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za UDP pratioce.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за УДП пратиоце.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za UDP pratioce.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för UDP-spårare</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">UDP izleme desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка координування UDP</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxUDP tracker supportxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持 UDP 追踪器</li>
      <li>Support for private trackers and torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="ast">Sofitu pa rastrexadores y torrents privaos</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport per a seguidors i torrents privats</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport per a seguidors i torrents privats</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für private Tracker und Torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη για ιδιωτικούς ανιχνευτές και torrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for private trackers and torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementación de rastreadores y torrents privados</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion des torrents et traqueurs privés</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade con localizadores e torrents privados.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per server traccia e torrent privati</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor privé-trackers en -torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa prywatnych serwerów śledzących i torrentów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para localizadores e torrentes privadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка частных трекеров и торрентов</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за приватне пратиоце и торенте.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za privatne pratioce i torente.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за приватне пратиоце и торенте.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za privatne pratioce i torente.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för privata spårare och dataflöden</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Özel izleyici ve torrent desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка приватних координаторів та торентів</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for private trackers and torrentsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持私人追踪器和种子</li>
      <li>Support for µTorrent's peer exchange</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport per a l'intercanvi entre parells de µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport per a l'intercanvi entre parells de µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Podpora výměny protějšků µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Austausch von Gegenstellen bei µTorrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη για ανταλλαγή µTorrent κόμβων</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for µTorrent's peer exchange</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementación de intercambio de pares de µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion de l'échange de pairs de µTorrent.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade co intercambio de parceiros de µTorrent.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per lo scambio di nodi con µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor uitwisseling van peers van µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa wymiany uczestników µTorrenta </li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para a troca de máquinas do µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка протокола обмена списками участников, используемого µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за Микроторентову размену вршњака.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za µTorrentovu razmenu vršnjaka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за Микроторентову размену вршњака.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za µTorrentovu razmenu vršnjaka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för µTorrents utbyte mellan deltagare</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">µTorrent eş değişimi desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка обміну вузлами у форматі µTorrent</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for µTorrent's peer exchangexx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持 µTorrent 对等点交换</li>
      <li>Support for protocol encryption (compatible with Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport per a encriptatge del protocol (compatible amb Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport per a encriptatge del protocol (compatible amb Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Protokollverschlüsselung (kompatibel mit Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη για κρυπτογράφηση πρωτοκόλλου (συμβατό με Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for protocol encryption (compatible with Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementación de cifrado de protocolo (compatible con Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion du chiffrement du protocole (compatible avec Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidade de cifrado do protocolo (compatíbel con Azureus).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per la cifratura del protocollo (compatibile con Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor protocolversleuteling (compatibel met Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa szyfrowania protokołu (zgodna z Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para a encriptação do protocolo (compatível com o Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка шифрования на уровне протокола (совместимо с Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за шифровање протокола (сагласна са Азуреусом).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za šifrovanje protokola (saglasna sa Azureusom).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за шифровање протокола (сагласна са Азуреусом).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za šifrovanje protokola (saglasna sa Azureusom).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för protokollkryptering (kompatibel med Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Protok şifreleme desteği (Azureus ile uyumlu)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка шифрування даних протоколів (сумісна з Azureus)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for protocol encryption (compatible with Azureus)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持协议加密 (兼容 Azureus)</li>
      <li>Support for creating trackerless torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport per a la creació de torrents sense seguidors</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport per a la creació de torrents sense seguidors</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für das Erstellen von Torrents ohne Tracker</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη για δημιουργία torrent χωρίς ανιχνευτές</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for creating trackerless torrents</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Admite la creación de torrents sin rastreadores</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion de la création de torrents sans traqueur</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidade de creación de torrents sen localizadores.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per la creazione di torrent senza server traccia</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor aanmaken van torrents zonder tracker</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa tworzenia torrentów bez serwera śledzącego</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para a criação de torrentes sem localizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка создания торрентов, не привязанных к торрент-трекеру.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за стварање торената без пратилаца.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za stvaranje torenata bez pratilaca.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за стварање торената без пратилаца.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za stvaranje torenata bez pratilaca.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för att skapa dataflöden utan spårare</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">İzleyicisiz torrentler için destek</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка створення торентів без координації</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for creating trackerless torrentsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持创建无追踪器种子</li>
      <li>Support for distributed hash tables (DHT, the Mainline version)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport per a taules de resum distribuïdes (DHT, la versió de la línia principal)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport per a taules de resum distribuïdes (DHT, la versió de la línia principal)</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Verteilte Hashtabellen (Distributed Hash Table, DHT in der Mainline-Version)</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήιριξη για κατανεμημένους πίνακες κατακερματισμού (DHT, η κύρια έκδοση)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for distributed hash tables (DHT, the Mainline version)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementación de tablas de resumen distribuidas (DHT, la versión principal)</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion des tables de hachage distribuées (DHT, la version principale)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade con táboas de sumas distribuídas (DHT, a versión principal).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per le tabelle di hash distribuite (DHT, la versione principale)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor gedistribueerde hash-tabellen (DHT, het hoofdversie)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa rozproszonych tablic haszów (DHT, wersja głównoliniowa)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para tabelas de dispersão distribuídas (DHT)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка распределённых хеш-таблиц (DHT).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за дистрибуиране дисперзионе табеле (мејнлајн ДХТ).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za distribuirane disperzione tabele (Mainline DHT).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за дистрибуиране дисперзионе табеле (мејнлајн ДХТ).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za distribuirane disperzione tabele (Mainline DHT).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för distribuerade kondensattabeller (DHT, huvudversionen)</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Dağıtık özet tabloları için destek (DHT, Ana sürümü)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка розподілених таблиць хешів (distributed hash tables або DHT, основної версії)</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for distributed hash tables (DHT, the Mainline version)xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持分布式哈希表 (DHT，主线版本)</li>
      <li>Support for UPnP to automatically forward ports on a LAN with dynamic assigned hosts</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport per a UPnP per desviar automàticament els ports de la LAN amb assignació dinàmica de màquines</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport per a UPnP per desviar automàticament els ports de la LAN amb assignació dinàmica de màquines</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für UPnP zur automatischen Port-Weiterleitung in Netzwerken mit dynamisch zugewiesenen Rechnern</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη UPnP για αυτόματη προώθηση θυρών σε τοπικό δίκτυο με δυναμική αντιστοίχιση υπολογιστών</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for UPnP to automatically forward ports on a LAN with dynamic assigned hosts</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementación de UPnP para redireccionar puertos automáticamente en una red local con servidores asignados dinámicamente</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion du protocole UPnP pour rediriger automatiquement des ports sur un réseau dont les hôtes sont gérés dynamiquement</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade con UPnP para redirixir automaticamente portos na rede local con servidores asignados dinamicamente.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto UPnP per mappare automaticamente le porte sulla LAN con host dinamici assegnati</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor UPnP om automatisch poorten te 'forwarden' op een LAN met dynamisch toegekende hosts</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa UPnP do przekierowywania portów w LANie z dynamicznie przypisanymi gospodarzami</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte de UPnP para encaminhar automaticamente os portos numa LAN para as máquinas atribuídas de forma dinâmica</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка UPnP для автоматического перенаправления портов в локальной сети с динамическим выделением IP-адресов.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за аутоматско прослеђивање портова кроз УПнП у ЛАН‑у са динамички додељиваним домаћинима.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za automatsko prosleđivanje portova kroz UPnP u LAN‑u sa dinamički dodeljivanim domaćinima.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за аутоматско прослеђивање портова кроз УПнП у ЛАН‑у са динамички додељиваним домаћинима.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za automatsko prosleđivanje portova kroz UPnP u LAN‑u sa dinamički dodeljivanim domaćinima.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för UPnP för att automatiskt vidarebefordra portar på ett lokalt nätverk med dynamiskt tilldelade värddatorer</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Dinamik olarak atanmış makineler ile LAN üzerinde otomatik port yönlendirme için UPnP desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка UPnP з метою автоматичного переспрямування портів у локальній мережі з динамічним призначенням назв вузлів</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for UPnP to automatically forward ports on a LAN with dynamic assigned hostsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持 UPnP 局域网自动转发端口的动态主机名</li>
      <li>Support for webseeds</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport per a sembradors web</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport per a sembradors web</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Webseeds</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη για πηγές ιστού</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Support for webseeds</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementación de semillas web</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion des sources web</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade con sementes web.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per distribuzione web</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor webseeds</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa rozsiewania w sieci</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para fontes Web</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка веб-сидов</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за веб сејања.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za veb sejanja.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за веб сејања.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za veb sejanja.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för webberbjudanden</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Web tohumları için destek</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка вебпоширення</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupport for webseedsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持 Webseed</li>
      <li>Scripting support via Kross, and interprocess control via D-Bus interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport per crear scripts a través de Kross i control entre processos a través de la interfície de D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport per crear scripts a través de Kross i control entre processos a través de la interfície de D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Skript-Unterstützung mit Kross und Interprozess-Steuerung über die D-Bus-Schnittstelle</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη συγγραφής σεναρίων με Kross και έλεγχος επικοινωνίας διεργασιών με D-Bus διεπαφή</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Scripting support via Kross, and interprocess control via D-Bus interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Admite el uso de guiones vía Kross y control de interprocesos vía la interfaz D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Scriptable par Kross et contrôle inter-processus par l'interface D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidade de scripting mediante Kross, e control entre procesos mediante unha interface de D-Bus.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per lo scripting tramite Kross, e per il controllo dei processi tramite interfaccia D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor scripts via Kross en interprocescontrole via het D-Bus-interface</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa skryptów przez Kross i sterowania międzyprocesowego poprzez interfejs D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte de programação através do Kross e controlo entre processos por uma interface de D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка сценариев при помощи Kross и внешнего управления через интерфейс D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за скриптовање преко Кроса и међупроцесно управљање преко д‑бус сучеља.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za skriptovanje preko Krossa i međuprocesno upravljanje preko D‑Bus sučelja.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за скриптовање преко Кроса и међупроцесно управљање преко д‑бус сучеља.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za skriptovanje preko Krossa i međuprocesno upravljanje preko D‑Bus sučelja.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Skriptstöd via Kross och styrning mellan processer via D-Bus gränssnitt</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kross üzerinden betik yazma desteği ve D-Bus arayüzü ile süreçler arası denetim</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка керування за допомогою скриптів на Kross та обміну даними між процесами за допомогою D-Bus</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxScripting support via Kross, and interprocess control via D-Bus interfacexx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">通过 Kross 支持脚本编程，通过 D-Bus 接口实现进程间控制</li>
      <li>System tray integration</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Integració amb la safata del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Integració amb la safata del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Integrace do systémové části panelu</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Integration in den Systemabschnitt der Kontrollleiste</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Ενσωμάτωση στο πλαίσιο συστήματος</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">System tray integration</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Integración con la bandeja del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Intégration dans la barre de notifications du système</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Integración coa área de notificación.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Integrazione nel vassoio di sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Integratie in het systeemvak</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Integracja z tacką systemową</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Integração na bandeja do sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Значок в системном лотке</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Уклапање у системску касету.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Uklapanje u sistemsku kasetu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Уклапање у системску касету.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Uklapanje u sistemsku kasetu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Integrering med systembricka</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Sistem çekmecesi tümleştirmesi</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість роботи у системному лотку</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSystem tray integrationxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">系统托盘整合</li>
      <li>Tracker authentication support</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Suport d'autenticació del seguidor</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport d'autenticació del seguidor</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Tracker-Authentifizierung</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη ταυτοποίησης ανιχνευτή</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Tracker authentication support</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Implementa autenticación del rastreador</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion de l'authentification des traqueurs</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidade de autenticación de localizadores.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporto per l'autenticazione sul server traccia</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Authenticatieondersteuning voor tracker</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsluga uwierzytelniania na serwerze śledzącym</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para localizadores autenticados</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка аутентификации на трекере.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за аутентификацију пратилаца.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za autentifikaciju pratilaca.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за аутентификацију пратилаца.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za autentifikaciju pratilaca.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för behörighetskontroll av spårare</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">İzleyici kimlik doğrulama desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка розпізнавання для координації</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTracker authentication supportxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">追踪器认证支持</li>
      <li>Connection through a proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="ast">Conexón pente un proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Connexió a través d'un servidor intermediari</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Connexió a través d'un servidor intermediari</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Připojení skrze proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Verbindung über Proxys</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Σύνδεση μέσω διαμεσολαβητή</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Connection through a proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Conexión a través de un proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Connexion à travers un proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Conexión mediante proxy.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Connessione attraverso un proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verbinding via een proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Połączenia przez serwer pośredniczący</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ligação através de um 'proxy'</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Подключение через прокси-сервер</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Повезивање кроз прокси.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Povezivanje kroz proksi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Повезивање кроз прокси.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Povezivanje kroz proksi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Anslutning via en proxy</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Vekil sunucu üzerinden bağlantı</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Встановлення з’єднання крізь проксі-сервер</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxConnection through a proxyxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">通过代理连接</li>
    </ul>
    <p>In addition to the built-in functionalities, there are some plugins available for KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Amás de la integración de funcionalidaes, hai dellos complementos disponibles pa KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Addicionalment a les funcionalitats integrades, hi ha diversos connectors disponibles per al KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Addicionalment a les funcionalitats integrades, hi ha diversos connectors disponibles per al KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Zusätzlich zu den eingebauten Funktionen gibt es weitere Module für KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Επιπλέον των ενσωματωμένων λειτουργιών, υπάρχουν κάποια πρόσθετα διαθέσιμα για το KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">In addition to the built-in functionalities, there are some plugins available for KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Además de las funcionalidades incluidas, hay varios complementos disponibles para KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">En plus de ces fonctionnalités internes, des extensions sont disponibles pour KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Ademais das funcionalidades incluídas, compatibilidade con complementos instalábeis desde KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">In aggiunta alle funzionalità integrate, ci sono alcune estensioni disponibili per KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Naast de ingebouwde functionaliteiten zijn er enige plug-ins beschikbaar voor KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dodatkowo do wbudowanych możliwości, dostępne są także wtyczki dla KTorrenta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Para além das funcionalidades incorporadas, existem alguns 'plugins' disponíveis para o KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Поред уграђених функција, доступни су и разни прикључци за К‑торент.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Pored ugrađenih funkcija, dostupni su i razni priključci za KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Поред уграђених функција, доступни су и разни прикључци за К‑торент.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Pored ugrađenih funkcija, dostupni su i razni priključci za KTorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Förutom inbyggd funktionalitet, finns några insticksprogram tillgängliga för Ktorrent.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Yerleşik işlevlere ek olarak, KTorrent için kullanılabilen bazı eklentiler de bulunmaktadır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Окрім вбудованих функціональних можливостей, у KTorrent передбачено розширення можливостей за допомогою додатків.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIn addition to the built-in functionalities, there are some plugins available for KTorrent.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">除了一些内置的功能，KTorrent 还有一些插件可用。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ktorrent</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/?application=ktorrent</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/ktorrent.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>ktorrent</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
